<root>
    <addition>
        <question>The ship must plan a journey that consists of two legs. The first leg is VAL_A lightyears long, and the second leg is VAL_B lightyears long. What is the length of the total journey in lightyears?</question>
        <question>You have recieved bonus vacation days! How many vacation days do you have in total, if you had VAL_A, and recieve a bonus of VAL_B?</question>
        <question>We are able to call two groups for backup. Group A consists of VAL_A ships, group B consists of VAL_B ships. How many ships do both groups have combined?</question>
    </addition>
    <subtraction>
        <question>We have VAL_A shield generators on board. VAL_B of them are damaged. How many shield generators are left?</question>
        <question>Our fuel reserves allow us to travel a distance of VAL_A units. We have already traveled VAL_B. In units, how much longer can we travel?</question>
        <question>Our journey requires us to visit VAL_A planets, of which we have already visitied VAL_B. How many more planets must we visit?</question>
    </subtraction>
    <multiplication>
        <question>The ship needs to visit VAL_A sectors to find all artifacts. Each sector contains VAL_B artifacts. How many artifacts does the ship need to find in total?</question>
        <question>The ship's central computer has VAL_A processors, each VAL_B cores each. How many processor cores does the ship's central computer in total?</question>
        <question>There are a total of VAL_A coalitions in the known universe, each consisting of VAL_B factions. How many factions are there in the known universe?</question>
    </multiplication>
    <division>
        <question>There are VAL_A ships in the fleet. How many ships would be in each division, if there were VAL_B divisions of equal size?</question>
        <question>Our weapon system is damaged! It used to boast VAL_A power units. Now it is equal to that value divided by VAL_B. How much power units is that?</question>
        <question>  </question>
    </division>
</root>